{
    "subject": "resource/Racey_Helps",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Bristol",
    "human_readable": "Racey Helps was born in Bristol.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9787649512290955,
            "question": "Is Bristol the city where Racey Helps was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9364594221115112,
            "question": "Is Racey Helps from Bristol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7927055358886719,
            "question": "Where was Racey Helps born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6615074872970581,
            "question": "What is the connection between Racey Helps and Bristol?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5334575176239014,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Racey Helps?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45917192101478577,
            "question": "What city is associated with Racey Helps' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4582163989543915,
            "question": "According to the information given, where did Racey Helps originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34361016750335693,
            "question": "Where did Racey Helps begin their life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3323681056499481,
            "question": "In which city did Racey Helps come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28029370307922363,
            "question": "What is known about Racey Helps' place of origin?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Racey Helps was born in Bristol.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4156_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In which city did Racey Helps come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4156_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where did Racey Helps begin their life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4156_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=According to the information given, where did Racey Helps originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4156_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_105.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_76.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4156_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Racey Helps was born in Bristol. This is explicitly stated in multiple documents, including file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4156/re-ranker-msmarco/55.txt and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4156/re-ranker-msmarco/76.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Angus Clifford Racey Helps was born in Bristol on February 2, 1913."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}